{
    "subject": "resource/Edgar_Rice_Burroughs",
    "predicate": "ontology/influenced",
    "object": "resource/Lin_Carter",
    "human_readable": "Edgar Rice Burroughs was influenced by Lin Carter.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9858739376068115,
            "question": "Was Lin Carter a source of inspiration for Edgar Rice Burroughs?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9420621991157532,
            "question": "What are some examples of how Lin Carter's influence is seen in Edgar Rice Burroughs' work?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9419254064559937,
            "question": "What is Lin Carter known for in relation to Edgar Rice Burroughs?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.937121570110321,
            "question": "Who influenced Edgar Rice Burroughs?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9020112156867981,
            "question": "Can you describe the connection between Edgar Rice Burroughs and Lin Carter?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8593184947967529,
            "question": "What is the relationship between Edgar Rice Burroughs and Lin Carter?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8266295790672302,
            "question": "Can you name someone who had an influence on Edgar Rice Burroughs?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8062810897827148,
            "question": "Who was influential in shaping Edgar Rice Burroughs' work?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6673427224159241,
            "question": "Who might have had an impact on Edgar Rice Burroughs' writing style?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5732737183570862,
            "question": "Did Edgar Rice Burroughs have any mentors or influences?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Edgar Rice Burroughs was influenced by Lin Carter.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7893_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who might have had an impact on Edgar Rice Burroughs' writing style?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7893_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who was influential in shaping Edgar Rice Burroughs' work?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7893_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you name someone who had an influence on Edgar Rice Burroughs?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7893_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7893_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7893_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7893_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7893_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7893_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7893_51.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7893_73.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7893_81.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7893_85.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7893_94.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation:\n\nThe documents provide information about Lin Carter's writing style and influences. It is stated that Edgar Rice Burroughs was a significant influence on Lin Carter's writing, particularly in his plotting and prose. This suggests that Edgar Rice Burroughs influenced Lin Carter, supporting the triple."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n```\n\nExplanation: The provided context does not suggest that Edgar Rice Burroughs was influenced by Lin Carter. Instead, the information indicates that Lin Carter was heavily influenced by Edgar Rice Burroughs, as it mentions \"Edgar Rice Burroughs may have had such an overwhelming formative influence on Carter that he was incapable of breaking free.\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": true,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Based on the given context, there is no information indicating that Edgar Rice Burroughs was influenced by Lin Carter. In fact, it's mentioned several times that Lin Carter was heavily influenced by Edgar Rice Burroughs in his writing style and choice of settings. Therefore, the triple \"Edgar Rice Burroughs was influenced by Lin Carter\" does not hold based on the provided information.\n\nThe answer is:\n```json\n{\"output\": \"no\"}\n```"
        },
        "llama3.1:70b": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'no'}"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": -1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "The provided text consistently describes Lin Carter as being heavily influenced by Edgar Rice Burroughs, citing similarities in plot structure, writing style, and even character archetypes.  There's no indication that the reverse is true.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "reason": "Lin Carter was heavily influenced by Edgar Rice Burroughs, as evidenced by the consistent use of similar themes and writing styles in his works.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}